let sample = [ 
    { "data": 
        { "id": "51", 
          "question": "fdkfkdnf", 
          "answer": "kfndkfn", 
          "information": "kfndkfn", 
          "rootId": "48" 
        } 
    }, 
    
    { "data": 
        { "id": "48", 
          "question": "AEAE3", 
          "answer": "AEAE", 
          "information": "AEAE", 
          "rootId": "48"
        } 
    }, 
    { "data": 
        { "id": "50", 
          "question": ",fdmsdkfm", 
          "answer": "mfndskfn", 
          "information": "jkfndskjfn", 
          "rootId": "48" 
        } 
    }, 
    { "data": 
        { "id": "52", 
          "question": "ndsfd", 
          "answer": "jjfndjfnsj", 
          "information": "jfndjsnf", 
          "rootId": "48" 
        } 
    }, 
    { "data": 
        { "id": "49", 
          "question": "jfhsdfjskd", 
          "answer": "jkfdskjfn", 
          "information": "kjfdnsjkf", 
          "rootId": "48" 
        } 
    }, 
    { "data": { "id": "53", "question": "kfjdkfnj", "answer": "njfdnjfn", "information": "jfndjfnj", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "54", "question": "ksmdkaldmk", "answer": "kdmskdm", "information": "kdmskd", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "55", "question": "Question", "answer": "Answer", "information": "Information", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "56", "question": "kdfmdkm", "answer": "kkfdmkfm", "information": "kfmdkfm", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "57", "question": "kfjskfdfm", "answer": "kfmdkmkf", "information": "kfmdkfm", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "58", "question": "test", "answer": "test", "information": "test", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "59", "question": "test", "answer": "test", "information": "test", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "60", "question": "test", "answer": "test", "information": "test", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "61", "question": "", "answer": "empty_node", "information": "", "rootId": "48" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-51", "source": "49", "target": "51" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-58", "source": "48", "target": "58" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-57", "source": "48", "target": "57" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-50", "source": "48", "target": "50" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-49", "source": "48", "target": "49" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-55", "source": "50", "target": "55" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-54", "source": "50", "target": "54" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-53", "source": "50", "target": "53" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-50", "source": "48", "target": "50" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-52", "source": "49", "target": "52" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-56", "source": "49", "target": "56" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-52", "source": "49", "target": "52" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-51", "source": "49", "target": "51" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-49", "source": "48", "target": "49" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-53", "source": "50", "target": "53" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-54", "source": "50", "target": "54" } }, { "data": { "id": "50-55", "source": "50", "target": "55" } }, { "data": { "id": "49-56", "source": "49", "target": "56" } }, { "data": { "id": "57-59", "source": "57", "target": "59" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-57", "source": "48", "target": "57" } }, { "data": { "id": "58-61", "source": "58", "target": "61" } }, { "data": { "id": "58-60", "source": "58", "target": "60" } }, { "data": { "id": "48-58", "source": "48", "target": "58" } }, { "data": { "id": "57-59", "source": "57", "target": "59" } }, { "data": { "id": "58-60", "source": "58", "target": "60" } }, { "data": { "id": "58-61", "source": "58", "target": "61" } } ]